ceo.ca 2017-02-10

# CEO.CA Privacy Policy, by @tommy

This Privacy Policy was last updated on February 4, 2017.  

This Privacy Policy is part of the Website’s Terms of Use (the “Terms”). Please note that all the capitalized terms not defined in this Privacy Policy are defined in the Terms.

The Operator respects and upholds an individual’s right to privacy and to protection of his or her Personal Information (as defined below). Should you choose to provide Personal Information to us, we will use reasonable security safeguards to ensure that your information is protected.

This Privacy Policy applies to all visitors to the Website, including both Members and non-Members. This Privacy Policy governs how the Operator collects, uses, and discloses Personal Information of visitors to the Website. Please note that this Privacy Policy applies only to information collected via the Website and does not apply to information obtained or disclosed in offline correspondence.

By using the Website, you acknowledge that you have reviewed the terms of this Privacy Policy and consent to the collection, use, disclosure, and transfer of your Personal Information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

1\. Definitions

“Member” means a person who is an individual who has satisfied all membership requirements by providing certain required Personal Information to the Operator for the purpose of gaining access to certain portion of the Website (such as chat.ceo.ca), and thereafter remains in good standing.

“Third Party” means an individual or an organization other than the Operator.

“Personal Information” means information about an identifiable individual as defined in applicable privacy legislation. It does not include aggregate information which cannot be associated with a specific individual and it does not include the name, title, business address, or business telephone number or other contact information about an individual at a place of business.

“Privacy Officer” means the person within the Operator’s organization responsible for the Operator’s compliance with this Privacy Policy.

“You” or “your” for the purposes of this Privacy Policy means visitors of the Website, including both Members and non-Members.

“Non-Professional” means any natural Person who is not a “securities professional”, in their personal capacity and not as a principal, officer, director, partner, employee or agent of any business or on behalf of any other Persons. A “securities professional” means any broker, dealer, investment advisor or Person, otherwise employed by an organization conducting professional activities involving the buying and selling of financial instruments, such as stocks, bonds, options, futures contracts or other trading vehicles. In addition, a Person shall not be considered Non-Professional if they are consultants, independent contractors, software developers or others that use Market Data for any purpose for profit other than the trading of a personal account. For greater certainty, a Non-Professional cannot be registered or qualified with:

  * (a) a provincial securities commission;   

  * (b) the Securities Exchange Commission;   

  * (c) the Commodities Futures Trading Commission;   

  * (d) any provincial, state or other government securities agency;   

  * (e) any securities exchange or association; or   

  * (f) any commodities or futures contract market or association or perform functions that are the equivalent to those of such Persons.   

2\. Accountability

The Operator is accountable for the Personal Information under its control. The Operator has appointed a Privacy Officer who is responsible for the Operator’s compliance with this Privacy Policy.

3\. Collection of Personal Information

Non-Members: When you browse the Website, you do so anonymously. The Operator does not collect Personal Information about you unless you voluntarily provide it to us when registering with the Website in order to access Members-only portions of the Website, submitting an inquiry to us, or for any other purposes that are identified when or before the time the Personal Information is collected.

Members: Where you interact with the Website to access those sections of the Website that are restricted to Members, we may ask you to register and/or sign in and we will collect certain Personal Information from you if you do so. The Personal Information that we may collect for this purpose may include your name, title, company, business address and phone number, and email address, and any other Personal Information that you choose to provide to us. The Operator collects this information for the purpose of enabling Members’ access to these restricted areas. Access is granted by submitting certain Personal Information for authentication.

Inquiries: You may submit an inquiry to us through the “Contact” link of the Website (ceo.ca/contact/). We may ask for certain Personal Information such as your name, e-mail address, and so on. We collect this information in order to enable us to respond to your inquiries in as thorough a manner as possible.

Server logs: Our servers automatically log information about visits to the Website in the normal course of establishing and maintaining web connections. The server logs record statistical information, such as visitors’ IP addresses, time and duration of visit, and websites visited. We collect this information so that we may continuously improve our Content. These statistics are reported in aggregate form only. We may process and use this aggregate data for various purposes, including, but not limited to, analysis of this data for trends and statistics, development of the Website and the Website’s features and offerings, assessing patterns of use, or planning and evaluating marketing initiatives. We do not link server log information to any other data in a way that would enable us to identify individual visitors.

Cookies: Cookies are small text files that contain a unique identifier that is placed on your computer. When you visit the Website, the Website saves the file with a matching identifier. When you revisit the Website days or weeks later, depending on the settings of your Internet browser, the Website may be able to recognize you by matching the cookie on your computer with the matching identifier in its database. Many Internet browsers are initially set to accept cookies. If you do not wish to accept cookies, you can set yours to refuse cookies or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If you reject cookies, you may be limited in using some areas of the Website.

4\. Use and Disclosure of Personal Information

We do not use or disclose Personal Information for any purposes other than those identified in this Privacy Policy, except with your consent or as required by law. We do not sell, lease, or trade information about you to other parties. Personal Information is retained only as long as is necessary for the fulfillment of the purposes identified in this Privacy Policy.

We may share (provide and receive) aggregate information, which is not personally identifiable, with others. This information may include demographic data such as the gender and/or geographic location of groups of Members and non-Members, but it will not include personal information (such as your name or email address). We may use aggregate demographic information about visitors to the Website in order to improve the services offered on the Website, for marketing purposes and/or industry reporting purposes. Where Personal Information is disclosed to Third Parties for the fulfillment of purposes described in this Privacy Policy, such Third Parties receiving the disclosed Personal Information will be contractually obligated to maintain confidentiality and security of the Personal Information and will be restricted from using such information in any way not expressly authorized by the Operator.

5\. Consent

By submitting Personal Information to the Operator, you agree that the Operator may collect your Personal Information and you consent to the use, disclosure, and transfer of your Personal Information in accordance with this Privacy Policy and as permitted or required by law. In addition, you represent and warrant that you have the right and authority or have obtained all necessary consents to provide any information, including any Personal Information of another individual that is provided by you to the Operator.

You may refuse or withdraw consent at any time, subject to legal and contractual restrictions and reasonable notice. You may refuse or withdraw your consent by contacting the Privacy Officer at the address listed below. Our Privacy Officer will explain your options and any consequences of refusing or withdrawing consent, and will record your choices.

6\. Accuracy

The Operator will make reasonable efforts to ensure that Personal Information is as accurate, complete, and current as required for the purposes for which it was collected. If you find any inaccuracies in our information, you can contact the Privacy Officer and we will make the appropriate corrections promptly.

7\. Safeguards

The Operator will use appropriate security safeguards to protect your Personal Information from risks such as unauthorized access, collection, use, disclosure, copying, modification or disposal or similar risks. Safeguards include physical, administrative, and electronic security measures. Nevertheless, Internet transmissions are never completely private or secure. You understand that any messages or information you send to the Website may be read or intercepted by others, and you should therefore take special care in deciding what information you send to us.

When we are required by law to provide information, we take reasonable steps to verify the lawful authority for the collection and we will disclose only the information that is legally required.

8\. Access

You have the right to access your Personal Information under the control of the Operator. Upon request in writing to the Privacy Officer at the address listed below, you will be informed of the existence, use, and disclosure of your Personal Information and you will be given access to that information. In certain exceptional situations, the Operator may not be able to provide access to certain Personal Information that it holds about you. For example, the Operator may not provide access to Personal Information if doing so would reveal Personal Information about another individual. If access cannot be provided, the Operator will notify you, in writing, of the reasons for the refusal and you may contact the Privacy Officer with respect to your questions about the refusal.

9\. Children

The Website is not directed to children under 18 years of age without appropriate parental notice and consent. Protecting the privacy of children is very important to us. We do not knowingly collect or maintain Personal Information from people under 18 years of age. If you are under 18, please do not send any information about yourself to us. In the event that we learn that we have collected Personal Information from a child under age 18 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information as quickly as reasonably possible.

10\. Opt-Out

When appropriate, Members of the Website are given the opportunity to either: (i) opt-out of receiving newsletters, alerts, bulletins, or other similar communications from the Operator or (ii) remove their Personal Information from the Operator’s records. If you wish to opt-out in the manner as listed above, please contact the Operator’s Privacy Officer at the address listed below.

11\. Links to Other Sites

The Website contains links to Third Party Websites. The Operator is not responsible for the collection of Personal Information or the security or privacy of such information on Third Party Websites. The Operator encourages you to request and review the privacy policies of any Third Party Websites. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected through the Website.

12\. Revisions to this Privacy Policy

The development of the Operator’s policies and procedures for the protection of Personal Information is an ongoing process. Due to changes in technology and legal requirements, we may revise this Privacy Policy from time to time, without prior notice to you. Please ensure that you refer to the current version of the Privacy Policy.

13\. Web Server Location

The web servers hosting the Website and your Personal Information are located in the United States. By using the Website and by voluntarily providing your Personal Information to us, you are consenting to the transfer of your Personal Information to the web servers hosting the Website in the United States. In addition, you acknowledge that your Personal Information may be available to the United States governments or agencies under a lawful order.

14\. Addressing your Questions or Concerns

If you have a question regarding this Privacy Policy or a concern or complaint regarding the privacy practices of the Operator, please contact the Privacy Officer by e-mail at info@ceo.ca, or by regular mail at:

1040 Palmerston Ave

West Vancouver, BC

V7S 2J3, Canada

Within a reasonable time upon receiving a written complaint, the Privacy Officer will conduct an investigation into the matter. Within a reasonable time of concluding the investigation, the Privacy Officer will inform you whether the complaint will be allowed or denied. If the Privacy Officer allows the complaint, the Operator will take appropriate measure necessary to rectify the source of the complaint.
